Guide to the Diacritics collection, [ca. 1971-2011]
Diacritics collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Diacritics collection, [ca. 1971-2011]
6988
16 cubic feet.
Correspondence, manuscripts, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records relating to the management of the journal. Includes administrative files, proofs and galleys, issues of Diacritics, submissions and reviews of articles. Also interviews with individuals involved in the publication.
Diacritics is a forum for scholars writing on the problems of literary criticism, based in the Dept. of Romance Studies at Cornell University, published by The Johns Hopkins University Press. It was founded in 1971 under the editorship of David Grossvogel.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records relating to the management of the journal. Includes administrative files, proofs and galleys, issues of Diacritics, submissions and reviews of articles. Also interviews with individuals involved in the publication.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Department of Romance Studies.
Subjects:
Criticism; Arts
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restriced to permission of the editor of Diacritics.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Administrative files
Boxes 1-2
Editorial board
Internal correspondence
Correspondence with Johns Hopkins
Other external correspondence
Subscriptions and publicity
Management and copyright issues
Article inventories
Editorial processes
Series II. Production
Boxes 2-6
Proofs and galleys
Design and layout
Art
Planning for special issues
Series III. Submissions and Reviews
Boxes 6-14
Evaluation files of accepted articles
Evaluation files of rejected articles
Series IV. Issues of Diacritics
Boxes 15-16
Series V. Interviews
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Administrative files
  - Editorial board
    - Board invitations and resignations, 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Invitations to join and requests to resign from the Diacritics editorial board
    - Minutes from board meetings, Various (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Editorial board--internal correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      internal correspondence pertaining to the Diacritics editorial board, often calls for meetings and descriptions of previous meetings.
  - Internal correspondence
    - Castillo internal correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
      internal correspondence from Diacritics editor Debra Castillo. Extensive and rich documentation of her (and assistant editor Kate Bloodgood's) attempts to reform the editorial processes of the Diacritics editorial board.
    - Richard Klein internal correspondence, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      internal correspondence from Diacritics editor Richard Klein.
    - Resina--Internal/editorial correspondence, Summer-Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Correspondence between editor Joan Ramon Resina and other members of Diacritics editorial board and staff.
    - Philip Lewis--Transition notes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes from outgoing editor Philip Lewis to new editor Debra Castillo to facilitate transition.
    - D. I. Grossvogel to unknown (Diacritics editor?) regarding metacriticism, ca. 2009 (Box 1, Folder 9a)
  - Correspondence with Johns Hopkins
    - JHUP-Diacritics marketing, 1982-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Correspondence between Diacritics and Johns Hopkins University Press regarding marketing. Several documents regarding advertisement exchanges with other journals.
    - JHUP-Financial correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Correspondence between Diacritics and Johns Hopkins University Press regarding the journal's finances.
    - JHUP-Other correspondence, 1979-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Administrative and other assorted correspondence between Johns Hopkins University Press and Diacritics.
  - Other external correspondence
    - Debra Castillo--external correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13-17)
      Correspondence between editor Debra Castillo and outside scholars. Many solicitations for review articles, notably from Rodolphe Gasché and Anthony Appiah.
    - Bruno Bosteels--external correspondence, Summer-Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Correspondence between editor Bruno Bosteels and outside scholars.
    - Joan Ramon Resina--external correspondence, Summer-Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Correspondence between editor Joan Ramon Resina and outside scholars.
    - Paper proposals, 1978-1993, 1978-1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Correspondence between editors Philip Lewis, Debra Castillo, Richard Klein, outside scholars, and staff and board members of Diacritics on proposals for review articles.
    - Resina paper proposals, 1998-2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Correspondence between editor Joan Ramon Resina, outside scholars, and staff and board members of Diacritics on proposals for review articles.
    - Philip Lewis--external correspondence, Summer-Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Correspondence between editor Philip Lewis and outside scholars.
    - Philip Lewis--Editorial correspondence, Summer-Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Correspondence between editor Philip Lewis and outside scholars, especially pertaining to revising submissions.
    - Jonathan Culler--Editorial correspondence, Summer-Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Correspondence between editor Jonathan Culler and outside scholars.
    - Article proposals to Debra Castillo, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 25-28)
      Proposals for review articles from outside scholars, often with extensive notes and/or back and forth correspondence with editor Debra Castillo and assistant editor Kate Bloodgood.
  - Subscriptions and publicity
    - Programs for Diacritics conferences, Various (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Management and copyright issues
    - Financial records, 1989-2009 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
      Various financial records from twenty years of the journal's history.
    - Editorial assistant position, 1986-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Details of tasks and hiring processes of editorial assistant.
    - Permissions requests, 1982-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Inquiries and responses to permissions requests
    - Legal documents, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Legal documents pertaining to the founding of Diacritics. Also includes the minutes of the first Diacritics board meeting in 1971.
  - Article inventories
    - Article inventories and indices, 1987-2009 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
      Inventories of articles published in Diacritics from 1987-2009.
  - Editorial processes
    - Submission style notes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Notes on style requirements for Diacritics submissions
- Series II. Production
  - Proofs and galleys
    - 23.2, Summer 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 24.2-3, Summer-Fall 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10-14)
      Special issue: "Critical Crossings"
    - 25.4, Winter 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
    - 26.1, Spring 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
    - 27.2, Summer 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 27.4, Winter 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 28.3, Fall 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Special issue: "Doing French Studies"
    - 28.4, Winter 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
      Special issue: "Trauma and Psychoanalysis"
    - 29.1, Spring 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 29.2, Summer 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 29.3, Fall 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
    - 29.3, Fall 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 29.2, Summer 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11-14)
    - 29.4, Winter 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15-19)
      Special issue: "Around the Work of Benedict Anderson"
    - 30.1, Spring 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
      Additionally contains some correspondence and examples of art used in the issue.
    - 30.3, Fall 2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 30.3, Fall 2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 30.4, Winter 2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 30.4, Winter 2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Earlier stage in editing process than other file of same name.
    - 31.1, Spring 2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 31.1, Spring 2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 31.3, Fall 2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 31.4, Winter 2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 32.3-4, Fall-Winter 2002 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
      Special issue: "Ethics"
    - 34.3-4, Fall-Winter 2004 (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
      Special issue: "Literary into Cultural Translation"
    - 35.1, Spring 2005 (Box 4, Folder 15-19)
      Special issue: "Essays in Memory of Pierre Klossowski"
    - 35.2, Summer 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - 35.2, Summer 2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Later in the design process than other file of same name.
    - 35.3, Fall 2005 (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
    - 35.4, Winter 2005 (Box 5, Folder 7-11)
      Special issue "Literature and the Right to Marriage"
    - 36.1, Spring 2006 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
    - 36.1 Final Proofs, Spring 2006 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 36.2, Summer 2006 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
      Special issue: "The Thought of Roberto Esposito"
    - 37.2-3, Summer/Fall 2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Special issue: "Taking Exception to the Exception"
    - 38.1-2, Spring/Summer 2008 (Box 6, Folder 6-9)
      Special issue: "Derrida and Democracy"
    - 38.3, Fall 2008 (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
  - Design and layout
    - 25.1 Design Proofs, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Proofs of Diacritics issue 25.1 featuring illustrations
  - Art
    - The Case for Books, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Undated photographs of bookshelves.
    - Miscellaneous Art, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Diacritics--Graphics, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Design notes for original format of Diacritics
  - Planning for special issues
    - Special issue proposal guidelines, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Guidelines for proposals for Diacritics special issues.
    - Correspondence on various special issues, 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Special issue proposal: African-American Thought, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Correspondence between Anthony Appiah and other intellectuals on possibility of a Diacritics issue devoted to African American thought and letters.
    - Special issue proposal: Descartes, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Proposal for special issue of Diacritics by Philip Lewis and Georges Van Den Abbeele devoted to Descartes.
    - Special issue proposal: Philippe Lacoue-Labarthe and Jean-Luc Nancy, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Proposal by Peter Fenves and Susan Berstein for a special issue of Diacritics issue devoted to the thought of Philippe Lacoue-Labarthe and Jean-Luc Nancy.
    - Special issue proposal: Views of America, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Proposal for special issue of Diacritics by Jose Piedra on America.
    - Special issue proposal: Latin American Literature, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      Proposal for special issue of Diacritics by Debra Castillo devoted to Latin-American Literature. Ultimately published as Diacritics 25.1, "Latin/American Issues"
    - Diacritics 25th Anniversary Issue, 25.2, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Internal and external correspondence planning the twenty-fifth anniversary issue of Diacritics, involving notes from board meetings, internal correspondence, and external solicitation of contributions.
    - Richard Klein--Nuclear Criticism, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      Draft and notes from Richard Klein's "Nuclear Criticism," an article that appeared in Yale French Studies but that can be read as a corollary to the special issue of Diacritics of the same name, 14.2.
    - Special issue proposal: Poetry Issue, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      Proposal from Jonathan Monroe for special issue of Diacritics: "Poetry, Community, and Movement." Ultimately published as Diacritics 26.3-4.
    - Special issue proposal: Bataille, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      Proposal from Nelly Furman for special issue of Diacritics devoted to Georges Bataille. Published as Diacritics 26.2
    - Special issue proposal: Irigaray Issue, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Proposal by Pheng Cheah and Elizabeth Grosz for special issue of Diacritics devoted to Luce Irigaray. Ultimately published as Diacritics 28.1.
    - Special issue proposal: Post-Mortem, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      Proposal for special issue of Diacritics by Jonathan Strauss on Death after the French Revolution. Ultimately published as Diacritics 30.3
    - Special issue proposal: Transgender Theory, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Proposal for special issue of Diacritics by Biddy Martin and Richard Juang on transgender theory
    - Special issue proposal: Anderson Issue, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Proposal for special issue of Diacritics by Jonathan Culler and Pheng Cheah on Benedict Anderson. Ultimately published as Diacritics 29.4.
    - Special issue proposal: Glas, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Proposal for colloquium on Jacques Derrida's Glas, on its 25th anniversary.
    - Special issue proposal: Rethinking Beauty, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      Proposal by Simon Jarvis for a special issue of Diacritics devoted to rethinking beauty. Eventually published as Diacritics 32.1
    - Special issue proposal: Marriage, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      Proposal by Steven Miller for a special issue of Diacritics devoted to Marriage. Eventually published as Diacritics 35.4.
    - Special issue proposal: Medieval Iberia, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      Proposal by Simone Pinet and Oscar Martin for a special issue of Diacritics devoted to Medieval Iberia. Published as Diacritics 36.3-4
    - Special issue proposal: Laruelle and Nonphilosophy, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      Proposal for a special issue of Diacritics devoted to François Laruelle and Nonphilosophy.
    - Special issue proposal: Said, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Proposal for a special issue by Namita Goswami of Diacritics devoted to Edward Said
    - Special issue proposal: Biopolitics and Roberto Esposito, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      Proposal from Timothy Murray for special issue of Diacritics devoted to biopolitics and the thought of Roberto Esposito, which would ultimately appear as Diacritics 36.2.
    - Special issue proposal: Rancière, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      Proposal from Bruno Bosteels for special issue of Diacritics devoted to Jacques Rancière and Politics.
    - Special issue proposal: Science, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
      Proposal from Jonathan Culler and Mark Seltzer for special issue of Diacritics devoted to science.
- Series III. Submissions and reviews
  - Evaluation files of accepted articles
    - Trevor Hope, "Sexual Indifference and the Homosexual Male Imaginary", Summer/Fall 1994 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      In Diacritics 24.2-3
    - Elizabeth A. Povinelli, "Sexual Savages/Sexual Sovereignty: Australian Colonial Texts and the Postcolonial Politics of Nationalism", Summer/Fall 1994 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - James Slawney, "Hallucinogenic Literature: Avital Ronell's Narcoanalysis", Winter 1994 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      In Diacritics 24.4
    - Jacques Derrida, "Archive Fever: A Freudian Impression", 1995 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      Highly significant piece by Jacques Derrida originally published in English in Diacritics 25.2. Presented here with correspondence regarding translation and the securing of rights.
    - Gordon C.F. Bearn, "Derrida Dry: Iterating Iterability Analytically", Fall 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      In Diacritics 25.3
    - Jill Robbins, "Circumcising Confession: Derrida, Autobiography, Judaism", Winter 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      In Diacritics 25.4
    - Steven Bretzius, "Dr. Jacques L. and Martin Hide-a-Guerre: The Subject of New Historicism", Spring 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      In Diacritics 27.1
    - Jonathan Loesberg, "Materialism and Aesthetics: Paul de Man's 'Aesthetic Ideology'", Winter 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      In Diacritics 27.4
    - Tom Conley, "Putting French Studies on the Map", Autumn 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      In Diacritics 28.3
    - Françoise Lionnet, "Reframing Baudelaire: Literary History, Biography, Postcolonial Theory, and Vernacular Languages", Autumn 1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - David Herman, "Parables of Narrative Imagining", Spring 1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      In Diacritics 29.1
    - Richard Burt and Jeffrey Wallen, "Knowing Better: Sex, Cultural Criticism, and the Pedagogical Imperatives of the 1990s", Spring 1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Patrick Paul Garlinger, "Homo-ness and the Fear of Femininity", Spring 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Amanda Anderson, "Realism, Universalism, and the Science of the Human", Summer 1999 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      In Diacritics 29.2
    - Carl Good, "Don Quijote and the Law of Literature", Summer 1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - E.C. Graf, "When an Arab Laughs in Toledo: Cervantes's Interpellation of Early Modern Spanish Orientalism", Summer 1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Doris Sommer, "Be-Longing and Bi-Lingual States", Winter 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      In Diacritics 29.4
    - David Kellogg, "Perloff's Wittgenstein: W(h)ither Poetic Theory?", Fall/Winter 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Draft titled "Avoiding the Subject: Marjorie Perloff and the Neutralization of Theory" ultimately published in Diacritics 26.3-4.
    - Michael Warner, "Van Winkle Family Values", July 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Evaluation file on accepted article ultimately not published in Diacritics.
    - Claudia Breger, "The Leader's Two Bodies: Slavoj Žižek's Postmodern Political Theology", Spring 2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      In Diacritics 31.1
    - Mark Hansen, "Seeing with the Body: The Digital Image in Postphotography", Winter 2001 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      In Diacritics 31.4
    - Esha Niyogi De, "Decolonizing Universality?", Summer 2002 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      In Diacritics 32.2
    - Ming Dong Gu, "The Universal "One": Toward a Common Conceptual Basis for Chinese and Western Studies", Summer 2002 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Stefano Franchi, "Hunters, Cooks, and Nooks: Two Interpretations of the Tangled Relationship between Philosophy and Science", Summer 2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      In Diacritics 33.2
    - Simon Critchley and Tom McCarthy, "Universal Shylockery", Spring 2004 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      In Diacritics 34.1
    - Leland de la Durantaye, "The Suspended Substantive: On Animals and Men in Giorgio Agamben's The Open", Summer 2003 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Kenneth Reinhard and Julia Reinhard Lupton, "The Subject of Religion: Lacan and the Ten Commandments", Summer 2003 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Ranjana Khanna, "Frames, Contexts, Community, Justice", Summer 2003 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Anne-Lise François, "'O Happy Living Things': Frankenfoods and the Bounds of Wordsworthian Natural Piety", Summer 2003 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Alexander E. Hooke, "Alphonso Lingis's We--A Collage, Not a Collective", Winter 2001 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Malcolm K. Read, "Benítez Rojo and Las Casas's Plague of Ants: The Libidinal Versus the Ideological Unconscious", Summer 2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - James Penney, "(Queer) Theory and the Universal Alternative", Summer 2002 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Tim Dean, "Art as Symptom: Žižek and the Ethics of Psychoanalytic Criticism", Summer 2002 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Ernesto Laclau, "Can Immanence Explain Social Struggles?", Winter 2001 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Denise Riley, "Bad Words", Winter 2001 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Judith Butler, "Giving an Account of Oneself", Winter 2001 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Brett Levinson, "Biopolitics and Duopolies", Summer 2005 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      In Diacritics 35.2
    - Orrin Wang, "Against Theory Beside Romanticism: The Sensation of the Signifier", Summer 2005 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Anjali Prabhu, "Interrogating Hybridity: Subaltern Agency and Totality in Postcolonial Theory", Summer 2005 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Anthony Sampson, "Freud on the State, Violence, and War", Fall 2005 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      In Diacritics 35.3
    - Kevin Lamb, "Foucault's Aestheticism", Summer 2005 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Michèle H. Richman, "Spitting Images in Montaigne and Bataille: For a Heterological Counterhistory of Sovereignty", Fall 2005 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Michael F. Bernard-Donals, "'Difficult Freedom': Levinas, Language, and Politics", Fall 2005 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Oliver Marchart, "In the Name of the People: Populist Reason and the Subject of the Political", Fall 2005 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Raphael Falco, "Arbitrary Cause", Summer 2005 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Mikko Tuhkanen, "Of Blackface and Paranoid Knowledge: Richard Wright, Jacques Lacan, and the Ambivalence of Black Minstrelsy", Summer 2001 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      In Diacritics 31.2
    - Charles Shepherdson, "A Pound of Flesh: Lacan's Reading of 'The Visible and the Invisible'", Winter 1997 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Elizabeth Maddock Dillon, "Fear of Formalism: Kant, Twain, and Cultural Studies in American Literature", Winter 1997 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Iain Morland, "Reading's Reason", Summer 2001 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Ignacio Javier López, "Film, Freud, and Paranoia: Dali and the Representation of Male Desire in 'An Andalusian Dog'", Summer 2001 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Amit Pinchevski, "Freedom from Speech (Or the Silent Demand)", Summer 2001 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Joseph Suglia, "The Communication of the Impossible", Summer 2001 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Brett Levinson, "Sex Without Sex, Queering the Market, the Collapse of the Political, the Death of Difference, and Aids: Hailing Judith Butler", Fall 1999 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      In Diacritics 29.3
    - Mark Sanders, "Reading Lessons", Fall 1999 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Bryan Reynolds and Joseph Fitzpatrick, "The Transversality of Michel de Certeau: Foucault's Panoptic Discourse and the Cartographic Impulse", Fall 1999 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Daniel Heller-Roazen, "Language, or No Language", Fall 1999 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Charles Stewart, "Syncretism and Its Synonyms: Reflections on Cultural Mixture", Fall 1999 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Neill Matheson, "Identifying (with) the Queerness of Melville's 'Pierre'", Winter 1997 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Barbara Johnson Papers, Spring 2004 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      Papers by Jonathan Culler, Judith Butler, Lee Edelman, and Jane Gallop ultimately published in Diacritics 34.1
    - Stewart Martin, "Adorno's Conception of the Form of Philosophy", Spring 2006 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      In Diacritics 36.1
    - Bruno Chaouat, "In the Image of Auschwitz", Spring 2006 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Carrie Noland, "Red Front/Black Front: Aimé Césaire and the Affaire Aragon", Spring 2006 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Kirk Wetters, "The Rule of the Norm and the Political Theology of 'Real life' in Carl Schmitt and Giorgio Agamben", Spring 2006 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - L. Scott Lerner, "Mourning and Subjectivity: From Bersani to Proust, Klein, and Freud", Spring 2007 (Box 7, Folder 59)
      In Diacritics 37.1
  - Evaluation files of rejected articles
    These papers are filed in mainly chronological order within the boxes.
    - Review files from rejected articles, 1986 - October 1996 (Box 8)
      Multiple submissions on Heidegger, Derrida.
    - Review files from rejected articles, November 1996 - April 1999 (Box 9)
      Multiple submissions on Heidegger, Butler, Deleuze, Derrida, Said, etc.
    - Review files from rejected articles, May 1999 - August 2000 (Box 10)
    - Review files from rejected articles, September 2000 - December 2002 (Box 11)
      Multiple submissions on Said, de Man, Irigaray, Derida, Žižek, Kant, Nancy, etc.
    - Review files from rejected articles, January 2003 - December 2004 (Box 12)
    - Review files from rejected articles, January 2005 - December 2007 (Box 13)
      Multiple submissions on Derrida, Deleuze, Wittgenstein, Kant, etc.
    - Review files from rejected articles, January 2008 - April 2010 (Box 14)
- Series IV. Issues of Diacritics
  - Issues of Diacritics 1.1-21.4, Fall 1971-Winter 1991 (Box 15)
  - Issues of Diacritics 22.1-41.1, Spring 1992-Spring 2013 (Box 16)
- Series V. Interviews
  - Interview with Philip Lewis with Laurent Ferri and Diane Brown, August 27, 2012; CD-1942